Guide to the Time Inc. Video Group Records 1934-1989 MS 3009-RG 41
New-York Historical Society
- Series IX. Time-Life Broadcast/Time-Life Broadcast Inc. Records, 1937-1974; 186897; 11.3 Linear feet in 13 records cartons
  Time Life Broadcast/Time-Life Broadcast Inc. Records cover the period of 1937 to 1974 with the bulk from 1961 to 1973. The focus of records is on sales and acquisitions of television stations, cable programming, and the production of the relaunch of March of Time.
  The Time Life Broadcast/Time-Life Broadcast Inc. Records are arranged into five subseries:
  Subseries IX.A. President Barry Zorthian Files
  Subseries IX.B. Vice President Edgar Smith Files
  Subseries IX.C. Purchase and Sale of State Records
  Subseries IX.D. Morrie Roizman March of Time Files
  Subseries IX.E. Mel Baily Files on "Crusade in Europe"
  - Subseries IX.A. President Barry Zorthian Files, 1968-1974; 185618; 4.3 Linear feet in 6 records cartons
    Biographical/Historical Note
    Barry Zorthian was hired as the president of Time-Life Broadcasting in 1969, succeeding Wes Pullen. Zorthian remained with Time-Life Broadcasting until 1972 when he became president of Time-Life Cable. In 1974, Zorthian is working as the deputy for public affairs for television and film group. By 1978, he has left his previous position and become vice president for government affairs under the director for corporate and public affairs within the corporate group. After 1978, he no longer appears on department head lists.
    The President Barry Zorthian Files cover the period of 1968 to 1974 and contain office subject and administration files, sales and acquisition information, and communications and information on Time-Life Broadcasting stations in various American cities: Denver, Indianapolis, San Diego, Grand Rapids, and Denver. Included in this series are prospective lists of officers and directors for sterling, project proposals, clippings, analysis of shareholder interest in sterling, press releases, meeting minutes, programming standards reports, reports on debenture accounts, engineering contract lists and schedules, franchised area maps, promotional materials, marketing reports, payroll reports, wage and price control reports, lists of stockholders, reports on public interest pamphlets, overtime summaries, clippings, Indianapolis chamber of commerce magazine issues, staff meeting summaries, Federal Communications Commission (FCC) reports, notes, budget reports, financial statements, Apollo 11 tv schedules, transmitter maintenance logs, rent appraisal reports, agreements, newspaper guild contracts, notes, lists of bonuses, and correspondence. The correspondence discuss cable financing, board meetings, pending projects, proposal criticisms, summary of suburban franchises, programming for public channel launches, comments on assembly bill, program costs, summary of lease, equipment purchases, subscriptions, account activities, job terminations, salaries, staffing, film production, agreements, opposition to company sale, equipment loan agreements, new ownership, television ads, story retraction, travel schedules, rental appraisal, press conference, personnel, severance, newspaper guild contracts, bonuses, meetings, project announcements, Nielsen scores, programming schedule, payments, licensing, and revenue.
    - Ackersan/Louisvile, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 1)
    - Ackersan/Louisville [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Ackersan and Wilson, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 2)
    - Ackersan and Wilson [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Alabama, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 3)
    - Alabama [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - ASCAP (American Society of Composers and Publishers) File: From B. Aubrey: 1973 October 25, 1968-1973; 185602 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 4-5)
    - ASCAP (American Society of Composers and Publishers) File: From B. Aubrey: 1973 October 25 [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Bakersfield: KERO-TV, 1971-1973; 185600 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 6-7)
    - Bakersfield: KERO-TV [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1971-1973; 185565 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors: Meetings Minutes, 1971-1973; 185592 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 9-10)
    - By-Laws, 1971 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 11)
    - CATV: Hearing, 1970 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 12)
    - CATV: Programming & Technical Standards, 1971-1972; 185569 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 13-14)
    - Comtel [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Converter: Correspondence, 1971-1972; 185570 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 15)
    - Co-op City, 1972 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 16)
    - Coudert Brothers, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 17)
    - Cravath, Swaine and Moore, 1971 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 18)
    - Cravath, Swaine and Moore [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Customer Complaints/Customer Relations, 1972-1973; 185571 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 19)
    - Customer Count/Customer Sales/Customer Disconnects, 1971-1972; 185572 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 20)
    - Data Processing Project/Computer Installation, 1972; 185573 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 21)
    - Debenture Accounts, 1972; 185574 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 22)
    - Denver: KLZ, 1971; 185564 (Offsite-box 3399, Folder 23-25)
    - Denver: KLZ, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 1-7)
    - Dever: KLZ [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Employees' Stock Purchase Plan [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Engineering, 1972; 185575 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 8)
    - Equipment, 1972; 185576 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 9)
    - Equipment: Letters, 1970-1971; 185595 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation: Fall [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - FCC/PB and D: Sterling [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Federal Income Tax File [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Galkin, Richard: Employment and Stock Option Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Offsite-box R61)
    - General Managers, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 11)
    - Goldwater and Flynn, 1971-1974; 185556 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 12)
    - Goldwater and Flynn [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Grand Rapids, 1973; 185563 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 13)
    - Grand Rapids [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Grand Rapids: WOOD, 1971-1973; 185562 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 14-15)
    - Grand Rapids: WOOD [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Grand Rapids: WOTV, 1972-1973; 185559 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 16-18)
    - Grand Rapids: WOTV: Package, 1973 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 19)
    - Indianapolis: WFBM, 1971; 185557 (Offsite-box 3400, Folder 20-21)
    - Indianapolis: WFBM, 1971-1973; 185558 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 1-3)
    - Indianapolis: WFBM [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Jasper CATV [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Jerrold Electronics [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Insurance: Director's & Officer's Liability for Sterling, 1972; 185577 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 4)
    - Legal Budget for Fiscal, 1973; 185579 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 5)
    - Louisville, 1973; 185566 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 6)
    - Madison Square Garden [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Manhattan/Sterling Cable, 1970-1971; 185567 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan/Sterling Communications Co. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Maps, 1971-1972; 185580 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 8)
    - Marketing/Sales/Sales Incentives, 1971-1972; 185581 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda, 1971 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1973; 185594 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 11-12)
    - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - N.Y. Financial Tax, 1970-1971; 185590 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 13)
    - Pay TV, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 14)
    - Pay TV [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Peoria, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 15)
    - Peoria [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Personnel, 1971-1973; 185555 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 16-17)
    - Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Pierson, Ball and Dowd, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 18)
    - Pierson, Ball, and Dowd [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Pricing, 1972; 185583 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 19)
    - Production Facilities, 1972; 185584 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 20)
    - Public Relations/Advertising/Community Relations, 1971-1973; 185585 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 21)
    - Public Relations/Advertising/Community Relations [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Raise Review, 1973 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 22)
    - Raise Review [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Real estate assets: Hopkins' Memorandum: 1970 October 6, 1970-1971; 185596 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 23)
    - Rochester, Inc., 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 24)
    - Rochester Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R61)
    - San Diego, 1968-1973 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 25)
    - San Diego: KOGO, 1971; 185553 (Offsite-box 3401, Folder 26-29)
    - San Diego: KOGO, 1971-1974; 185554 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 1-2)
    - San Diego: KOGO [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Southern Cable Company [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Sterling: Converter Patent [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Sterling: Leasing Office Space, 1972; 185578 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 3)
    - Sterling: Stock Option [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Sterling Communications, 1971; 185591 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 4)
    - Sterling Communications [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Sterling Information Services: Board of Directors Minutes, 1970; 185568 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 5)
    - Stock Reports/Stockholders, 1971-1973; 185586 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 6)
    - Stockholders: Thomajan, P.K., 1972-1973; 185587 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 7)
    - Studio Facilities, 1971-1972; 185588 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 8)
    - Survey of Community Needs: Time-Life Broadcast Stations to Pierson, Ball, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 9-11)
    - Telco, 1971-1972; 185589 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 12)
    - Teleguide, 1972 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 13)
    - Time-Life Broadcast Stations: Fall Programming Adjustments, 1971; 185598 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 14)
    - Time-Life Broadcast Stations: Political Conventions, 1971-1972; 185597 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 15)
    - Time-Life Broadcast Stations: Volunteer Consumer Protection Memorandum: 1972 March 1, 185599 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 16)
  - Subseries IX.B. Vice President Edgar Smith Files, 1962-1965; 187151; 1.8 Linear feet in 3 records cartons
    Edgar P. Smith joined Time Inc. in 1946 and was assistant managing editor of Fortune in 1955, when he conceived the ''500'' listing, which became an annual feature of the magazine. He went on to become managing editor of Architectural Forum, which spawned House & Home in 1952, "for those who plan, build, buy, sell, and finance new houses". He was appointed the vice president in charge of cable development for Time-Life Broadcast in 1962 and laid the groundwork for Time Inc.'s entry into cable television. When Time Inc. made the decision to invest in community antenna television (CATV) during the 1960s, Smith led the move to scout out potential properties.
    The Vice President Edgar Smith Files cover the period of 1962 to 1965 and consist of one box of materials regarding cable programming during the beginning of his time as vice president of Time-Life Broadcasting. Included in this series are budget reports, notes, clippings, schedules, show overviews, promotional brochures, and correspondence. Correspondence discusses agreements between Time and Sims Production, proposed agreements, co-operation for Tokyo Olympics radio programs, contact information, sponsor interest, brochure production, previews, and future projects.
    - Americans Abroad, 1964; 187152 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 17)
    - Air Force Show, 1964; 187153 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 18)
    - Auto Racing, 1963; 187154 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 19)
    - Back to Back, 1964; 187162 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 20)
    - Bakersfield, 1963-1964; 187205 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 21)
    - Berlin '63, 1962-1963; 187155 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 22)
    - Business series: Grace story, 1963; 187156 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 23)
    - Business series: Schwartz Pilot, 1963-1964; 187157 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 24)
    - Business Series: Schwartz Pilot [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Civil Rights, 1963-1964; 187207 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 25)
    - Courtship, 1964-1965; 187163 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 26)
    - Courtship Releases [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Cyprus, 1964; 187158 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 27)
    - Ecumenical Century, 1963; 187159 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 28)
    - Ecumenical Century [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Eddie Condon, undated; 187160 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 29)
    - Educational Films, 1962-1964; 187208 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 30)
    - E.P.S.: Miscellaneous TV File, 1962; 187211 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 31)
    - Film Survey on Cyprus, 1964; 187161 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 32)
    - A Game Called Football, undated (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 33)
    - Grand Award of Sports, 1963-1965; 187167 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 34)
    - Grand Award of Sports [RESTRICTED], 1964-1965 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Hallmark, 1963; 187212 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 35)
    - Indianapolis 500, 1964-1965; 187164 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 36)
    - Iraq: Overseas Directors, 1963; 187165 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 37)
    - Life History series, 1964-1965; 187168 (Offsite-box 3402, Folder 38)
    - MacArthur Series, 1963; 187213 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 1)
    - Men of Fortune, 1963-1965; 187169 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 2)
    - Miss Lillian Smith of Georgia, 1963-1965; 187170 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 3)
    - Miss Lillian Smith of Georgia [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Perspective, 1964-1965; 187171 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 4)
    - Perspective [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R62)
    - PGA Golf Tournament, 1963; 187214 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 5)
    - Political Conventions, 1963-1964; 187172 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 6-7)
    - Press, 1963; 187215 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 8)
    - Programming, 1963-1964; 187173 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 9-10)
    - Promotion, 1963-1964; 187216 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 11)
    - QXR: Tom Wise, 1963-1964; 187174 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 12)
    - SEC Report, 1963; 187175 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 13)
    - Sims, Paul: Kenyon and Eckhardt, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 14)
    - Sims, Paul: Kenyon and Eckhart [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R62)
    - SLAARS: Monte Carlo TV Festival: New Ark, 1962-1964; 187176 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 15-16)
    - Study of the Book Publishing Industry, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 17)
    - Syndication, 1964; 187177 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 18)
    - Time Cover Story: Mayor Daley of Chicago, 1963; 187217 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 19)
    - Time Music Review Show [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Tokyo Olympics, 1964; 187179 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 20)
    - Topics and Trends, 1962-1963; 187180 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 21)
    - Vietnam: Lodge, 1963-1964; 187181 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 22-23)
    - Vietnam: Lodge [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Voices in the News, 1963; 187182 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 24)
    - World's Fair, 1964; 187183 (Offsite-box 3403, Folder 25)
  - Subseries IX.C. Purchase and Sale of Stations Records, 1961-1972; 191512; 1.2 Linear feet in 2 records cartons
    Time-Life Broadcast, Inc. contains bound volumes of purchase and sale documents for various business deals of this subsidiary. Eacg volume contains agreements related to the sale or purchase of assets. Several volumes are embossed with "John F. Harvey," the Time Inc. comptroller. There is some crossover with RG 5: Series I.C.: Dead Companies.
    Organized chronologically.
    - Acquisition of Assets of KOGO Broadcasting Corporation and Related $6,000,000 Bank Loan [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962; 191520 (Offsite-box R62)
    - Sale of Assets of WTCN-AM / Sale of Stock of TLB, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1964; 191519 (Box 618, Folder 1)
    - Acquisition of 25,000 shares of Common Stock of The Jackson TV Cable Company [RESTRICTED], 1966; 191518 (Box 618, Folder 2)
    - Purchase of 85 Shares of Common Stock of KAOK-CATV, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967; 191517 (Box 618, Folder 3)
    - Purchase of Common Stock of Philadelphia Community Antenna Television Company [RESTRICTED], 1967; 191516 (Box 618, Folder 4)
    - Purchase of 34-1/6 Shares of Common Stock of Ashtabula Cable TV, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967; 191515 (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - Acquisition of Agoura CATV System [RESTRICTED], 1970; 191514 (Box 618, Folder 6)
    - Sale of Assets Constituting Radio Stations KLZ-AM and FM to Group One Broadcasting Co. [RESTRICTED], 1972; 191513 (Box 618, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IX.D. Morrie Roizman March of Time Files, 1937-1964; 3 Linear feet in 3 records cartons
    Morrie Roizman began working for Time-Life Broadcast in 1959 as a consultant, producer, and editor on March of Time and other Time-Life Broadcasting television films. In 1960 he begins working as an independent contract on Time in Perspective. After working on that project, Roizman leaves Time Inc. but returns in 1964. From 1964 to 1969, Roizman work for Time-Life Broadcasting in their program production department. During this time, he worked on the attempted relaunch of March of Time.
    FYI: Issues. Time Inc. Reference Files (MS 3009-RG 3), New-York Historical Society.
    The Morrie Roizman Files cover the period of 1937 to 1964 with the bulk covering 1961 to 1962. The materials included in this subseries focus on creating scripts for an attempted relaunch of March of Time. Included in this subseries are scripts, drafts of scripts, clippings, lists of scenes, lists of research information, and audio reels.
    - Additional Materials: Communications, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 1)
    - Additional Materials: Correspondence, 1962 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 2)
    - Additional Materials: Film Survey on Cyrus, 1964 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 3)
    - Additional Materials: Finished Business, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 4)
    - Additional Materials: Footnotes, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 5)
    - Additional Materials: The Golden Twenties, 1959 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 6)
    - Additional Materials: Hands That Made America, 1958 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 7)
    - Additional Materials: Kid Stuff, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 8)
    - Additional Materials: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 9)
    - Additional Materials: Miscellaneous: Storage, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 10)
    - Additional Materials: Picture Source Lists, 1962 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 11)
    - Additional Materials: Research Papers, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 12)
    - Additional Materials: Science, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 13)
    - Additional Materials: Townsend and Child Labor, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 14)
    - Additional Materials: Transportation, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 15)
    - Additional Materials: Uncle Sam Laughs, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 16)
    - Additional Materials: Unfinished Business, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 17)
    - Completed Shows: An Era Begins, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 18)
    - Completed Shows: An Era Begins: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 19-20)
    - Completed Shows: Aspect of Youth, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 21)
    - Completed Shows: Danger Spots, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 22-23)
    - Completed Shows: Filler: Odd Paragraphs, undated (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 24)
    - Completed Shows: For the Common Defense, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 25)
    - Completed Shows: The Hungry Years, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 26)
    - Completed Shows: The Little Flower, 1961 (Offsite-box 3404, Folder 27)
    - Completed Shows: The New Deal, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 1)
    - Completed Shows: The New Deal: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 2)
    - Completed Shows: The Noisemakers, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 3)
    - Completed Shows: The Noisemakers: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 4-5)
    - Completed Shows: Rehearsal for Peace, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 6)
    - Completed Shows: Rehearsal for Peace: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 7)
    - Completed Shows: Rehearsal for War, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 8)
    - Completed Shows: Rehearsal for War: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 9)
    - Completed Shows: Rise of Labor, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 10)
    - Completed Shows: Royalty, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 11)
    - Completed Shows: Royalty: Scripts, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 12)
    - Completed Shows: Too Much and Not Enough, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 13)
    - Completed Shows: Trial and Error, 1961 (Offsite-box 3405, Folder 14)
    - Recorded Audio: Aspects of Youth, 1961 December 18 (Offsite-box R63, Item 1)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On side of box: "Aspects of Youth". On back of box: "7.5 IPS 'March of Time' 'Aspect of Youth' 12-18-61".
    - Recorded Audio: Danger Spots, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Danger Spots From The March of Time". On side of box: "March of Time 'Danger Spots' ".
    - Recorded Audio: An Era Begins, 1961 December 27 (Offsite-box R63, Item 3)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 4 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Morrie Roizman 1600 BWay NYC Room 312". On box: "7 1/2 i.p.s. 'An Era Begins' TK.2. Opening TK.3. Insert 61-v-898 Produced By: The March of Time Dec. 27, 1961"
    - Recorded Audio: An Era Begins, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 4)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On side of box: "The March of Time - An Era Begins". On back of box: "An Era Begins".
    - Recorded Audio: For the Common Defense, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 5)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On box side: "For the Common Defense". On back of box: "61V871 March of Time 7 1/2 IPS 'For the Common Defense' ".
    - Recorded Audio: The Hungry Years, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 6)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "The Hungry Years From The March of Time". On side of box: "M.O.T. 'The Hungry Years' ". On back of box: "7 1/2 M.O.T. 'Hungry Years' ".
    - Recorded Audio: The Little Flower and The Little Project, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 7)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "The Little Flowe and The LIttle Project From The March of Time". On side: "The Lttle Flower and The Little Project".
    - Recorded Audio: The New Deal, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 8)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On side of box: "March of Time 'The New Deal' ". On box back: "March of Time 'New Deal' ".
    - Recorded Audio: The Noisemakers, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 9)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On side of box: "The March of Time 'The Noisemakers' (Gerald LK. Smith)".
    - Recorded Audio: The Noisemakers, undated (Offsite-box R63, Item 10)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On side of box: "M.O.T. 'The Noisemakers' 7 1/2 ips 61V931". On back of box: "61V931 M.O.T. 'The Noisemakers' 7 1/2 IPS".
    - Recorded Audio: Rehearsal for War, 1961 October 19 (Offsite-box R63, Item 11)